When you go through the university,
whether it's four years or whatever time
you spend there, those are arguably the
most formative years of your life.
It sets the stage for what the rest of
your career is going to be.
I'm blessed to be surrounded by thousands of the
smartest aerospace engineers in the world.
I always tell my management team
you can't be a good manager if you don't
understand what it is you're you're
managing, and so you have to continue to learn.
One great thing about engineers is
they're great teachers, so every day I
learn something new from our engineers.
One thing that's great about being a Hawkeye is no matter where you go, wherever you go, and I've walked
on the walls of Beijing and right there is
someone wearing a Hawkeye shirt.
They're everywhere and they stay together
Once a Hawkeye always a Hawkeye
and wherever you live we still have that
bond that brings us together.